guesthouser.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - GuestHouser

GuestHouser is devoted to protecting the privacy of our customers and users. Any information that is stored, collected, or shared will be handled with absolute compliance with personal data protection laws. During the registration process, personal information is collected to better connect members with matching accommodations or customers. All members have the access to a limited profile that will not be shared publicly, but only from host to customer or customer to host after a booking request has been submitted. Periodically, user information will be collected for analytics for GuestHouser to measure our site performance and statistics and shared with trusted third-parties in order to improve the site and the overall user experience; however, this will never reveal your identity.

####  Data Provided During The Registration Process

All customers and users that provide their personal information necessary for the registration process shall do so voluntarily. During the booking process, personal information like your name, address, email, and telephone number will be shared between host and customer in order to confirm a booking request and to address backend enquiries. All personal and financial details that are provided to complete the booking request shall be given voluntarily. We will only use these details to complete the booking process and will not used for any other purpose. GuestHouser reserves the right to revise or change our Privacy Policy at any point. 

#### Eligibility:

All users, whether registered or not, agree to the Privacy Policy by using the site, application, or services. All users are required to be 18 years of age or older. By using the site, application, and services, the user confirms that they are 18 years of age or older. Registering for Email Subscription: Our emails are voluntary and are used to provide our members with updates on popular listings and site news. Users can unsubscribe from GuestHouser emails by clicking unsubscribe at the bottom of any of the emails.

#### Facebook Integration:

Connecting your Facebook with GuestHouser will provide us with some information that will be used for analytics. It is up to the user's choice to integrate Facebook with their GuestHouser account for convenience, and this service can be canceled at any point in user settings. If given permission, GuestHouser will post on your wall on your behalf about your latest activity on the site. Again, this option is optional and can be disabled at any point in the user settings.

##### Cookies:

GuestHouser uses cookies and other similar technologies on the Platform. We may also allow our business partners to use their cookies and other tracking technologies on the Platform. As a result, when you access or use the Platform, you will provide or make available certain information to us and to our business partners. While you may disable the usage of cookies through your browser settings, we do not change our practices in response to a "Do Not Track" signal in the HTTP header from your browser or mobile application. We track your activities if you click on advertisements for GuestHouser services on third party platforms such as search engines and social networks, and may use analytics to track what you do in response to those advertisements.

##### Security:

All online transactions on GuestHouser are secure as they are protected and encrypted with SSL technology. This ensures that once a submission is made, the data is scrambled before it travels over the internet. Information is collected using secure password protection. GuestHouser will not be held responsible for loss, misuse or unauthorised use of personal information by third parties, in spite of all necessary measures having been taken for bona fide protection of customers' data.

#### How To Change Personal Information Or Delete Account

All users can access their user settings and profile editor to edit/change their personal information, and to further change their privacy settings.  In order to delete your account, go to the bottom of the user settings page and push delete account, then follow the instructions that will lead you through the rest of the process. 

#### Profiles

Every member profile will show limited personal information, except for the information that establishes you as a real human being, like your name, description, and any other information you choose to display. A member's full profile will only be displayed during a booking request to both the host and the guest.

#### Have Any Feedback?

Feel free to shoot us an email at [ support@guesthouser.com ](mailto:support@guesthouser.com)
